#### **PROFILE**

Hello, my name is Anaisa, but I go by Isa. I am a 31-year-old woman, currently residing in North Rhine-Westphalia. However, I will be relocating to Munich in early December. Throughout my life, I have worked in the hospitality industry, but I have always been intrigued by IT professions. Earlier this year, I decided to take on a new challenge and switch to a career in technology.

I am a team player and an independent worker, a fast learner, and highly organized. I have a strong work ethic and always give 100% to new professional challenges. I adapt easily to new situations and work environments, and I attribute these qualities to the various work scenarios I have experienced.

#### **PROFESSIONAL QUALITIES**

- ✔Organisation
- ✓ Work ethic
- ✓Team spirit
- ✓Initiative
- ✔Dedication and Effort
- ✓ Fast Learner
- ✔Attention to detail
- ✓Punctual

### **ANAISA PEDRO**

Address: Einsteinstraße 4681675 Munich

Phone nr: +49 1638068364 Email: isa.pedro92@hotmail.com Portfolio: https://main--portfolio-anaisa-pedro.netlify.app/

GitHub: https://github.com/lsapedro

### **EDUCATION**

freeCode Camp 11/23

ResponsiveWeb Design

**SheCodes**, 14/08/23 - 15/10/23

SheCodes Basics and SheCodes Basics Add-on,

SheCodes Plus and SheCodes Plus Add-on,

SheCodes Responsive and SheCodes Responsive Add-on,

SheCodes React and SheCodes React Add-on,

SheCodes Next.

Google Digital Academy(Skillshop) 08/23

Fundamentals of digital marketing

OnHair Academy, Algés, 12/2020-09/2021

Professional Barber Training

Finishing with 17 Values.

SVQ - Scottish Vocational Qualifications 01/2014 - 10/2014

Modern Apprenticeship in Hospitality Supervision and Leadership

Finishing with 80 credits e SCQF level 7

Escola Secundária de Silves-2008 - 2011

Language and Humanities Course

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

### Eis Cafe San Remo, Coesfeld NRW, Germany

Eiskellnerin\_01/03/23 - 30/09/23

Worked full time in a family owned business in a Ice cream cafe and bistro only for the high season. This job was mainly for adaptation to moving in to Germany.

### Xilb Barber and Lounge Bar, Silves, Portugal

Barber and Bartender 16/01/2022 - 30/09/2022

Started this job as a barber but soon after become also bartender after the barbershop working hours. Worked with a team of 2 other professionals in the barbershop and become person responsible for the closing of the bar.

### Barbairos, Barbearia e Garrafeira, Alfragide, Portugal

Barber 06/09/2021-30/12/2021

Started with a part-time in this barbershop while I was finishing the course of barber in the Onhair Academy. Becoming a full timer in October. Worked with a team of 3 professionals who supported me in every way possible of the start of the career path of barbering. It was a short experience due to needing to move back to my hometown. But deepen my knowledge and technics in "hot towel" shaving and perfected the hair cuts with razor machines and scissors given attention to what the client wanted.

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- ✓ Management
- ✓ Communications
- ✓ Critical thinking
- ✔Front-end development
- ✔Wireframe Creation
- ✔Project management tools
- ✔Problem solving,
- ✓VS Code, Git
- **✓**GitHub,
- ✓ Bootstrap
  ✓ Hosting,
- ✓HTML + CSS, JavaScript,
- **✓**React.js
- ✓ API,
- ✔Responsive Development,
- ✓ Strong Communication

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Fundamental of Digital Marketing - 14/08/23

Introduction to Coding - 19/08/23 Introduction to Web Development - 22/08/23

Web Development - 06/09/23 Advanced Web Development - 08/09/23

**Responsive Web Development -** 21/09/23

Advanced Responsive Web
Development - 25/09/23
React Development - 05/10/23
Career Development - 14/10/2023
Advanced React Development - 16/10/23

Responsive Web Design - 25/11/23

#### **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese - native English - fluent Spanish - competent Italian - basic German - basic

#### Dishoom, Edinburgh, Scotland

Server 06/19-08/20

Cocktail Bartender 12/18 - 06/19

I've started my career with this restaurant chain as a bartender where I continued to develop my knowledge and execution of all the drinks specified for the restaurant. When an opportunity came up to progress to a server position I decided I should try and was the successful one. This positions are solely internal applications due to the high level of knowledge you are needed to have about all the products, ingredients and drinks. Working in Dishoom was a very fundamental enriching experience that I enjoyed a lot.

### Old Poison Company, Edinburgh, Scotland

Sales Assistant/Bartender - 01/2018- 11/2019

Work alongside with a Gin based distillery as a sale assistant, in advertising the brand, in pop up cocktail bars/events. During this time I was helping in the preparation for the events and making of the drinks using the gin. (Selkie Gin)

## The Refinery, Edinburgh Scotland

Cocktail Bartender Supervisor 10/2017 - 08/2018

Has cocktail bartender in The refinery I was quickly promoted to supervisor due to my organisation and previous team supervision experience. Has a supervisor I had the responsibility of ordering stock, checking the deliveries, supervise guide and teach the new member of staff, and cash up.

#### The Brunswick Pub, Brighton, England

Bar Supervisor 01/2018-09/2018

I was employed as part time bar staff then promoted to full time supervisor.

Duties Included: Training new staff members, overlooking trial shifts. Also cellar trained.

### Radisson Blu Hotel, Edinburgh Scotland

<u>Supervisor of the Bar</u>: Itchycoo Kitchen and Bar 09/2016 - 11/2016 <u>Supervisor Breakfast Room - The Restaurant 09/2015 - 09/16</u>

Shift-Leader: 10/2013 - 09/2015

Room-Service attendant 03/2012 - 10/2013

Server 10/2011 - 03/2012

Finalist for Carlson Rezidor Supervisor/ Shift Leader Shining Star of the Year 2015, across Great Britain, finishing on top 4.